Miller, J. Gormly Papers /4133
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
J. Gormly Miller Papers
1959-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Miller, J. Gormly
/4133
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
8016742
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 13, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4170: J. Gormly Miller Additional Papers
Miller, J. Gormly
8016742
- International Labor Office. Central Library and Documentation Branch Correspondence. J G Miller, 1970-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Libraries Automated Acquisitions System Manual of Procedures, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ILR 590 "Report Writing", 1949-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ILR 391 "Sources and Materials in Labor Relations", 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR 391 "Sources and Materials in Industrial and Labor Relations", 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR. Feasibility Study of Centralized Information Services in Industrial Relations (Barhydt Report), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  May 8 1968
- ISI/ILO Project, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "The Production of Economic Literature: An Interpretation" Michael C Lovell, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  March 1973
- "The Production of Economic Literature: An Interpretation" Michael C Lovell and Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILO Library. National Bureau of Economic Research. 1971. "Workshops on Computers and the Documentation of Information", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Special Projects. ILO Library Survey, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  April 15 - May 24 1964
- "Report on Proposed Space Program for U.S. Department of Labor Library", 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  August 1 1965
- "Report to the Director-General of the International Labor Office of a Survey of the ILO Library and a Review of its Program", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  May 21 1964
- "The Framework of Personnel Administration in the Special Library" (Box 1, Folder 14)
  J Gormly Miller
- "Report to the Secretary of Labor on the Proposed Establishment of the Labor Library and Information Center in the Puerto Rico Department of Labor", 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  September 1965
- Gormly Miller. "IV The Staff and Plant of Special Libraries, B. Personnel", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  February 13 1962
- "Report on the Library Program of the Department of Labor Relations of INSORA", 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  January 15 1962
- "Report on Relationship Between Main Library, Law Library and Legislative Reference Service within U.S. Tariff Commission", 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  July 3 1967
- "Report to the Director-General of the International Labor Office of a Survey of the ILO Library and a Review of its Program", 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- "Directory of United Nations Serial Publications", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  United Nations, New York.
- 'Register of United Nations Serial Publications", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Inter-Organization Board for Information Systems. July 1982
- "Directory of United Nations Databases and Information Systems", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  United Nations, New York
- U.S. Department of Labor. Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Labor. General., 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Includes Time Records
- Photograph (Box 2, Folder 6)
  A photograph of a model of a building
- U.S. Department of Labor. Correspondence and General, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Labor. Building Project. Current Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- U.S. Department of Labor Project. Library and Reference Services. Current Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- U.S. Department of Labor Documentation, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- U.S Department of Labor. Interim Reports and Documents, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- U.S. Department of Labor. Material Relating to Question of "National Library", 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- U.S. Department of Labor. Budget and Salary Data, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  "A functional Analysis of the Department of Labor Library". July 1966
- U.S. Department of Labor. "Federal Department Libraries" (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Evans
- J.G. Miller. Personal, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- "Proposal for A Bibliographical Survey of Serial Publications from Labor Organizations Outside the Western Hemisphere", 1962-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- J.G. Miller. General Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Contains one photograph
- Office of Manpower, Automation and Training. Clearing House of Research and Information, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Washington, DC. December 9 1963
- B-20 Faculty. J G Miller, Personal, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- B-20 Faculty. J G Miller, Personal, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- B-20 Faculty. J.G. Miller, Personal, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- B-20 Faculty. J G Miller, Personal, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- J Gormly Miller. General Correspondence, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Miller, J Gormly. General Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Miller, J Gormly. General Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bureau of Adult Education, State Education Department, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Union Francaise des Organismes de Documentation, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  French and English
- Universite de Paris, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  French.
- B-70 Course Material. ILR 590. Outlines, Schedules, etc., 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Outlines, Notes and Schedules, 1946-1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Library Journal. Volume 67. No. 15., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  September 1 1942
- ILR 590. Written Communications (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Miller, J Gormly. Personal, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- ILR 590. Schedule of Course Meetings (Box 3, Folder 20)
- ILR 391 Sources and Materials in Labor Relations". Documents, 1950-1956 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- J.G. Miller. Personal, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- B-70. ILR 590. Course Materials, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- B-70. ILR 590. Outlines and Schedules, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Fall 1959 - 1960
- J. Gormly Miller Correspondence and Newspaper Clipping, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- "The Framework of Personnel Administration in the Special Library" Draft (Box 3, Folder 26)
- "Manpower, Wages and Labor Relations in World War II: An Annotated Bibliography", 1951 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Cornell University. Bulletin 19. 2 copies
- "Sources of Information on Union-Management Relations"\, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Extension Bulletin No 4. March 1950. J Gormly Miller. New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University
- "Labor Resources in the Cornell University Libraries", 1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- "Labor History" Volume 1, Number 3., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Fall 1960
- "Les Etudes dans Les Universites", 1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  French. Ministere des Affaires Etrangeres Direction Generale des Relations Culturelles, Bureau de Documentation. Fenruary 1 1949
- "La Premiere Internationale" Periodiques, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  French
- ILR 391. Documents, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- ILO and LABORDOC. Abstracting Project. Proposal, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ILO/ISIS. Processing System. Acquisitions and Cataloguing Module, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  June 1972
- US Department of Labor. Development Grant Proposal Documents, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ILO/ISIS Processing System, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- CUL. ILR. ISIS. US Department of Labor Project. Current Documents and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- CUL. ILR. ISIS. US Department of Labor. Background Material, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- CUL. ILR. ISIS Plan. US Department of Labor Background Material, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  November 30 1976
- "Labor-Industrial Relations Information Service: A Draft Proposal", 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- CUL. ILR. ISIS Plan. US Department of Labor Proposal Documents, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- US Department of Labor. Industrial Relations Serials Project for CONSER Database, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- "Proposal for Microcomputer-based System for Library Cost Analysis and Decision Support", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Segment I: Progress Report on Statistical Reporting System for Library Activities and Programs
- Library Management Services ILR Project. Proposal to CUL and other CUL-Related Activities, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  October 1984
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting Systems. ILR Decision Support System Project Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Library Management Services ILR/DSS Project. Proposal to the Council on Library Resources, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  June 1984
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Preliminary Proposal Documents and Reference Documents, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Segment I Progress Report, Miscellaneous Support Documents, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  August 1984
- Library Management Services. Statistical Reporting System ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, Acquisition Data Files, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, Field Definition Tables, Templates, File Directories, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Spring 1985
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. ILR Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Statistical Reporting Systems. Working Papers, Acquisitions, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, Acquisitions Data Files II, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Statistical Reporting Systems. Working Papers, Catalog Data File, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Statistical Reporting Systems. Working Papers, Circulation Data File, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Statistical Reporting Systems. Working Papers, Reference Data File, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. File Directory (1-2-3 Diskettes), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  July 1984
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Library Statistical Reporting System. Working Papers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  September 1983
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, Register of Date Elements, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, Internal Data Cell Forms, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  May 18 1983
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. Working Papers, External Reporting Forms, 1982- 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. Reference Documents, Library Systems, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  December 3 1982
- Library Management Services. ILR/DSS Project. Reference Documents, ALA. Research Department, Mary Jo Lynch. Data Cell Handbook, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. Reference Documents, Forms. Data Collection., 1982- 1985 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Library Management Services. Library Statistical Reporting System. ILR/DSS Project. General Reference Documents, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  August 1983
- US Department of Labor. ILR Information System. Abstract Preparation Project. Reference Documents, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- DF. Systems. Reference Documents. I.P. Sharp, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- US Department of Labor. ILR Project. Supplementary Material and Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- ILR. CIRL. Newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- CIRL Meeting. Cornell University. ILR Library, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  May 27 - 29, 1981
- DF. US Department of Labor Project and CIRL Meetings. Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Washington, 1980.
- US Department of Labor and CIRL Meeting. Documents and Reports for CIRL Meeting, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Toronto, May 29 - June 1 1979
- CUL/DF. CUIRL Meeting, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  May 6 - 7 1976
- DF. ILR. THESAURUS. Report to CUIRL Meeting., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Ottawa, June 1975
- Committee of University Industrial Relations Librarians. 29th Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Ottawa, June 19 - 20 1975
- DF. US Department of Labor/ISIS Project. CUIRL, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- US Department of Labor. Contract No. T9M80216. Final Report and Official Copy, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  September 29 1978
- U.S. Department of Labor. Contract No. T9M80216. Final Report and Accompanying Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Tape Description: June 24 1980. Contract: September 29 1978
- US Department of Labor. Contract No. T9M80216. Final Report and Accompanying Documents, Training Manual, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- US Department of Labor. Contract No. T9M80216. Reports, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Contract: September 29 1978
- US Department of Labor. Contract Documents. "Preparation of Abstracts of Labor Relations Literary Publications since 1976", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Contract T9M80216, dated September 29 1978
- US Department of Labor. Contract No. T9M70114. Final Report. Version A with Appendices. Version B without Appendices., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  January 1980
- US Department of Labor. Contract No. J9M70114. Final Report, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- US Department of Labor. Contract J9M70114. Final Report. Draft for Review, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  January 24 1980
- US Department of Labor. Contract J9M70114. Final Report. Appendices, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  December 1978
- Re-Typed Pages and Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- US Department of Labor. Contract Documents. Contract No. J9M70114. "Labor Industrial Relations Information System for the US Department of Labor and its Regions", 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  September 27 1977
- US Department of Labor. Contract J9M70114. Final Report. Working Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- US Department of Labor. Contract Documents. Proposed, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  June 1979
- ILR-ILO/ISIS. US Department of Labor Project. GK Thompson. Current Working Papers, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- US Department of Labor. ILR Information System and Abstract Preparation. Current Working Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- CUL Directors File. ILR Thesaurus Project, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Advisory Committee for the Coordination of Information Systems. Newsletter, 1982- 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  November 1982 - January 1992
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Advisory Committee for the Coordination of Information Systems., 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Advisory Committee for the Coordination of Information Systems. Special Problems, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  May 1989
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Information Systems Unit Project. Official Documents and Communications, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Information Systems Unit. Final Report, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  April 30 1983
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Information Systems Unit. Final Report. Official Lang=uages other than English, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Spanish, Russian, French, Arabic, Chinese. December 3 1983
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Information Systems Unit. Expense Account, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Labor Management Services. United Nations. Information Systems United Project. ISW Official Reports, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  March, April and June 1983
- J.G. Miller. Current Working Folder, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- International Social Science Journal. Reference Documents: American Behavioral Scientist. American Documentation, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  June 1970
- "Traditional Documentation Processes in the Social Sciences", 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  June 16 1970
- C-60. Special Projects. Handbook for Special Libraries. JG Miller, 1962-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Special Projects. "Handbook for Special Libraries". "The Framework of Personnel Administration in the Special Library". Draft, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- International Labor Office. Correspondence, 1961-1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- International Labor Office. Central Library and Documentation Branch. Documents and Reports (Box 6, Folder 15)
- International Organizations other than the ILO, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Spanish and English. November and December 1964
- Special Projects. Puerto Rico Department of Labor. Library and Information Center, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  November 1965
- Puerto Rico Department of Labor. Staff and other Individuals, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  August 1965
- Puerto Rico Department of Labor. Miscellaneous Materials, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Puerto Rico Department of Labor. Draft Report and Preliminary Documents, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Puerto Rico Department of Labor. Contract, Travel Arrangements, etc., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  August to November 1965
- US Department of Labor Project. Reference Documents and Materials. ILO, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  June, September and October 1965
- US Department of Labor. Library Program Comments and Criticism, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  November and December 1966
- Reports on a National Library, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Miller, J.G. Publications and Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  January 15 1962. August 1965
- "Report on Space Requirements for Law Library US Department of Labor", 1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  August 10 1965
- "US Department of Labor Space Program and Sketch Plans for Library", 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- US Department of Labor. Library Program. Draft Report, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  June and July 1967
- US Department of Labor. Library Project Legislative Proposals with Reference to Merger of US Department of Labor and Department of Commerce, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  January - February 1967
- US Department of Labor Project. Reference Documents and Materials. Non-US Government, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- US Tariff Commission Library Project, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  June 1967
- US Department of Labor. Research Inventory and Clearinghouse for Department Research, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- US Department of Labor. Reference Documents (US Government), 1959-1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)